A Finding Aid to the Leo Castelli Gallery Records, circa 1880-2000, bulk 1957-1999, in the Archives of American Art AAA.leocast
Archives of American Art
- Castelli Graphics, circa 1950-1999, bulk mid 1970s-early 1990s; Series 7; (Boxes 154-169; 16 linear feet)
  - Correspondence, 1969-1996; 7.1
    - Lowe, Brian, 1990 (Box 158, Folder 100)
    - Lowenadler, Jan Eric - Galerie Lowenadler AB, 1971-1973 (Box 158, Folder 101)
    - Ludwig, Georg, circa 1988 (Box 158, Folder 102)
    - Ludwig, Dr. Peter, 1969-1971, 1974 (Box 158, Folder 103)
    - Lupke, Klaus, 1970-1971, 1974 (Box 158, Folder 104)
    - Lynch, Joseph W., Jr., 1974 (Box 158, Folder 105)
    - Lyss, Esther, 1990 (Box 158, Folder 106)
    - M, 1969-1974 (Box 158, Folder 107)
    - M, 1975, 1977-1979 (Box 158, Folder 108)
    - M, 1979-1981, 1991 (Box 158, Folder 109)
    - Malloy, Meg, 1991, 1993 (Box 158, Folder 110)
    - Mangisch, Rudolf, 1992 (Box 158, Folder 111)
    - Marcus, Michael, 1992 (Box 158, Folder 112)
    - Marian Goodman Gallery, 1990 (Box 158, Folder 113)
    - Marilyn Finkel and Associates, 1993 (Box 158, Folder 114)
    - Marion Koogler McNay Art Institute, 1970, 1977-1978 (Box 158, Folder 115)
    - Mark Gallery, 1972 (Box 158, Folder 116)
    - Marshall, Judith, 1992 (Box 158, Folder 117)
    - M'arte, 1969-1971 (Box 158, Folder 118)
    - Masheck, Joseph, 1992 (Box 158, Folder 119)
    - Mass Mailing, 1977-1981 (Box 158, Folder 120)
    - Matsumoto, Yoshiko, 1992 (Box 158, Folder 121)
    - Maubrie, Gabriella - Hans Namuth, 1992-1993 (Box 158, Folder 122)
    - Maubrie, Gabriella - Robert Rauschenberg, 1993 (Box 158, Folder 123)
    - Mayer, Francoise, 1972-1973 (Box 158, Folder 124)
    - Mayer, Robert B., 1971-1973 (Box 158, Folder 125)
    - McBain, Morgan, 1990 (Box 158, Folder 126)
    - McCall, David, 1973-1974 (Box 158, Folder 127)
    - McCleaf Gallery, 1970 (Box 158, Folder 128)
    - McDougal, Ann - Lee Bontecou, 1992 (Box 158, Folder 129)
    - McMenamin, Regina - The Four Seasons, 1994 (Box 158, Folder 130)
    - Media Gallery, 1974 (Box 158, Folder 131)
    - Meehan, Michael, circa 1992 (Box 158, Folder 132)
    - Menschel, Joyce and Bob, circa 1992 (Box 158, Folder 133)
    - Merce Cunningham Dance Foundation, Inc., 1990-1992 (Box 158, Folder 134)
    - Merlin House, 1980 (Box 158, Folder 135)
    - The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1977-1981 (Box 158, Folder 136)
    - Metzdorff, Gerd, 1978-1979 (Box 158, Folder 137)
    - Meyer, Eric, 1969-1970 (Box 158, Folder 138)
    - Middleton, Ian, 1982, 1984, 1988, 1992 (Box 158, Folder 139)
    - Midland Group Gallery, 1970 (Box 158, Folder 140)
    - Milant, Jean R., 1972-1974, 1979-1980, 1994 (Box 158, Folder 141)
    - Miller, Bill - Ellsworth Kelly/Jasper Johns, 1992 (Box 158, Folder 142)
    - Miller, Ellen - Miller Block Gallery, 1993 (Box 158, Folder 143)
    - Miller, Michele - Roy Lichtenstein, 1992 (Box 158, Folder 144)
    - Milwaukee Art Center, 1970, 1979-1980 (Box 158, Folder 145)
    - Minkel, Herbert P., Jr., 1993 (Box 158, Folder 146)
    - The Minneapolis Institute of Arts, 1970 (Box 158, Folder 147)
    - Misani, Marco, 1978-1979 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Monsen, Joseph, 1979-1981 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Morgan Art Gallery, 1970-1971, 1977-1978 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Morrison, Bob - List, 1993 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Muhlenberg College, 1973 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Multiples Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Multiples Inc., 1974-1976 (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - Multiples Inc., 1977-1979 (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Mulvaney, Jay - Robert Rauschenberg, 1992 (Box 159, Folder 9)
    - Muniz, Vik, 1990 (Box 159, Folder 10)
    - Munson Gallery, 1973-1974 (Box 159, Folder 11)
    - Musée Cantini, 1979-1980 (Box 159, Folder 12)
    - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, 1991 (Box 159, Folder 13)
    - The Museum of Modern Art, 1970-1972, 1978-1979 (Box 159, Folder 14)
    - The Museum of Modern Art, 1989-1991 (Box 159, Folder 15)
    - Myers, Chris - Roy Lichtenstein/Andy Warhol, 1993 (Box 159, Folder 16)
    - N, 1970-1981 (Box 159, Folder 17)
    - NABIS Fine Arts, Inc., 1971 (Box 159, Folder 18)
    - Nakaya, Fujiko, 1973-1974 (Box 159, Folder 19)
    - Namuth, Hans, 1991-1992 (Box 159, Folder 20)
    - National Gallery of Art, 1973-1974, 1990 (Box 159, Folder 21)
    - Navarro, Albert, circa 1992 (Box 159, Folder 22)
    - Nehm, Otto, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 23)
    - The New Gallery, 1970-1973, 1979 (Box 159, Folder 24)
    - Newport Harbor Art Museum, 1970 (Box 159, Folder 25)
    - New York City Art Gallery Price Watch, circa 1988 (Box 159, Folder 26)
    - New York Print Weekend, 1993 (Box 159, Folder 27)
    - Niikura, Kakuko, 1991 (Box 159, Folder 28)
    - Nishizawa, Midori - Akira Ikeda Gallery, 1993 (Box 159, Folder 29)
    - Notkin, Richard, 1993 (Box 159, Folder 30)
    - Numark, Cheryl, 1994 (Box 159, Folder 31)
    - Nuzzolo, Joe, 1993 (Box 159, Folder 32)
    - Nydens, Kent A. - Novo Art, 1971-1972 (Box 159, Folder 33)
    - O, 1970-1974 (Box 159, Folder 34)
    - O, 1977-1981 (Box 159, Folder 35)
    - Obalne Galerije Piran, 1993 (Box 159, Folder 36)
    - O'Brian, C. Michael, 1994 (Box 159, Folder 37)
    - One Hundred Hearts, 1993 (Box 159, Folder 38)
    - Oosterbos, Peter, 1980-1981 (Box 159, Folder 39)
    - Opitz, Marika - Roy Lichtenstein, 1993 (Box 159, Folder 40)
    - Oratz, Roz - Roy Lichtenstein/Robert Rauschenberg, 1993 (Box 159, Folder 41)
    - Ordover, Jerald, 1993 (Box 159, Folder 42)
    - Osborne, Michael - Robert Rauschenberg, circa 1993 (Box 159, Folder 43)
    - O'Toole-Edwald Art Associates, Inc., 1993 (Box 159, Folder 44)
    - P, 1969-1973 (Box 159, Folder 45)
    - P, 1977-1981 (Box 159, Folder 46)
    - Pace Prints - Jasper Johns, 1993 (Box 159, Folder 47)
    - Pacific Press Service, 1991 (Box 159, Folder 48)
    - Paine Webber, 1992-1994 (Box 159, Folder 49)
    - Panza, Giuseppe, 1989 (Box 159, Folder 50)
    - The Parrish Art Museum, 1978-1980 (Box 159, Folder 51)
    - Patton, Tom, 1977-1978 (Box 159, Folder 52)
    - People Taking Action Against Aids, 1990 (Box 159, Folder 53)
    - Perucchi, Ursula - Kunsthaus Zürich, 1990 (Box 159, Folder 54)
    - Pettibone, Jean K. - Richard Artschwager, circa 1992 (Box 159, Folder 55)
    - Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1970-1971 (Box 159, Folder 56)
    - The Photographers' Gallery, Canada, 1978 (Box 159, Folder 57)
    - The Photographers' Gallery, London, 1977-1980 (Box 159, Folder 58)
    - Photographers' Gallery and Workshop, 1978-1979 (Box 159, Folder 59)
    - The Photography Gallery, 1980 (Box 159, Folder 60)
    - Picture Magazine, 1979-1981 (Box 159, Folder 61)
    - Tony Pintauro - Andy Warhol, 1992 (Box 159, Folder 62)
    - Plakke/Jacobs Fine Arts Photography, 1990 (Box 159, Folder 63)
    - Platzker, David - List, 1992 (Box 159, Folder 64)
    - Plehn, Cynthia, 1992-1994 (Box 159, Folder 65)
    - Plummer, Mrs. M. Q., 1993 (Box 159, Folder 66)
    - Polack, Clark, 1971-1973 (Box 159, Folder 67)
    - Polaroid Corporation, 1978-1980 (Box 159, Folder 68)
    - Pomona College, 1974 (Box 159, Folder 69)
    - Poncy, Pat, 1992 (Box 159, Folder 70)
    - Powers, George, 1992 (Box 159, Folder 71)
    - Pratt Graphics Center, 1973-1974 (Box 159, Folder 72)
    - Preutz, Lennart, 1994 (Box 159, Folder 73)
    - Princeton University, 1971, 1977, 1980 (Box 159, Folder 74)
    - The Print Club, 1969-1971, 1973 (Box 159, Folder 75)
    - Printworld - Joseph Kosuth, 1990 (Box 159, Folder 76)
    - Protetch-Rivkin, 1971 (Box 159, Folder 77)
    - Punkenhofer, Dr. Robert - List, 1992 (Box 159, Folder 78)
    - Q, 1969-1970, 1978 (Box 159, Folder 79)
    - Quad Graphics, 1987 (Box 159, Folder 80)
    - R, 1969-1974 (Box 159, Folder 81)
    - R, 1976-1981 (Box 159, Folder 82)
    - Rabinowitz, Leah and Allan - Jasper Johns, circa 1992 (Box 159, Folder 83)
    - Ralston, Peter, circa 1989 (Box 159, Folder 84)
    - Rankow, Leslie, 1989, 1991-1993 (Box 159, Folder 85)
    - Rapoport, George, 1992 (Box 159, Folder 86)
    - Rapp, Carol, 1990 (Box 159, Folder 87)
    - Rapp, Morton H., 1969-1970, 1973 (Box 159, Folder 88)
    - Ratcliffe, Albert, 1989 (Box 159, Folder 89)
    - Ratzer, Peter, 1981, 1984, 1991 (Box 159, Folder 90)
    - Rauschenberg, Robert, 1978-1980 (Box 159, Folder 91)
    - Rawle, David - Flag I and II (Simca), 1973-1978 (Box 159, Folder 92)
    - Raymond Foye Editions, 1987-1990 (Box 159, Folder 93)
    - Rayton, Kenneth - Jasper Johns, 1992 (Box 159, Folder 94)
    - Renner, Eric, 1978-1979 (Box 159, Folder 95)
    - Retif, Earl, 1973-1974 (Box 159, Folder 96)
    - Reynolds Gallery - Damaged Loan, 1990-1992 (Box 159, Folder 97)
    - Richard Bauer and Co., Inc., 1979 (Box 159, Folder 98)
    - Richard Green Gallery, 1990 (Box 159, Folder 99)
    - Ricke, Rolf - Galerie Ricke, 1970-1973 (Box 159, Folder 100)
    - Rimbaud, Robin, 1989 (Box 159, Folder 101)
    - Robbins, Judy, 1979 (Box 159, Folder 102)
    - Robert Freidus Gallery, 1980 (Box 159, Folder 103)
    - Roberts, Sandra Montoya, 1989 (Box 159, Folder 104)
    - Robinson, Joan Seeman, 1989 (Box 159, Folder 105)
    - Rocchetti, Giorgio, 1975-1976 (Box 159, Folder 106)
    - Roeder, Margarete, 1993 (Box 159, Folder 107)
    - Rogoff, Barbara, 1994 (Box 159, Folder 108)
    - Romley, Paul - Roy Lichtenstein, circa 1992 (Box 159, Folder 109)
    - Ronald Feldman Gallery, 1993 (Box 159, Folder 110)
    - Ronis, Elma - Annex Gallery; San Diego, CA, 1991 (Box 159, Folder 111)
    - Rosen, Randy - Ellsworth Kelly/Robert Lichtenstein, 1992-1993 (Box 159, Folder 112)
    - Rosenbach, Detlev - Galerie Rosenbach, 1971 (Box 159, Folder 113)
    - Rosenbaum, Arthur and Sandra - Roy Lichtenstein, circa 1992 (Box 159, Folder 114)
    - Ross, Joanna - Andy Warhol, 1993 (Box 159, Folder 115)
    - Ross, Mindy - Ellsworth Kelly, 1993 (Box 159, Folder 116)
    - Rousseau, Nicole - List, 1992 (Box 159, Folder 117)
    - Rudler, Roderick, 1971 (Box 159, Folder 118)
    - Rudzinoff, Viviane, 1980 (Box 159, Folder 119)
    - Ruscha, Edward, 1976-1979 (Box 159, Folder 120)
    - Russo, Karen, 1993 (Box 159, Folder 121)
    - S, 1969-1974 (Box 159, Folder 122)
    - S, 1977-1978 (Box 159, Folder 123)
    - S, 1978-1979, 1990 (Box 159, Folder 124)
    - La Salita Arte Contemporanea, 1970-1971 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Salita, Wayne J., 1989 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Samuels, Leslie B., 1990 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Sanada, Ikkan, 1988-1989 (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - San Francisco Museum of Art, 1970-1973, 1979 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco Museum of Modern Art, 1979, 1989 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Scharf, Uta, 1992 (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Schefler, Arno, 1993 (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - Schellmann, Jörg, 1970, 1974 (Box 160, Folder 9)
    - Schellmann, Jörg - Verlag Schellmann and Klüser, 1972, 1979 (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - Schlier, Debbie, 1992 (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - Schlossberger, Karish, 1990 (Box 160, Folder 12)
    - The Scholar's Bookshelf, 1989 (Box 160, Folder 13)
    - Schouela, Ezekiel, 1989 (Box 160, Folder 14)
    - Schramm, James S., 1969-1970, 1972 (Box 160, Folder 15)
    - Schreiber, David, 1978 (Box 160, Folder 16)
    - Schuchart, Migs, 1979-1980 (Box 160, Folder 17)
    - Schuster, Madelene, 1990 (Box 160, Folder 18)
    - Schwartz, Elliot, circa 1976-1978 (Box 160, Folder 19)
    - Schwartz, Estelle, 1978-1980, 1992 (Box 160, Folder 20)
    - Schweber, Kenneth, 1991-1992 (Box 160, Folder 21)
    - Scott, Andrea - Viart Corporation, 1993 (Box 160, Folder 22)
    - Screen Printing Association International, 1970-1971 (Box 160, Folder 23)
    - Sebastien, M. Lifshitz, 1989 (Box 160, Folder 24)
    - Segal, Thomas and Ronnie - Thomas Segal Gallery, 1977-1979, 1981 (Box 160, Folder 25)
    - Selcow, Leslie, 1990 (Box 160, Folder 26)
    - Self, Robert, 1978-1979 (Box 160, Folder 27)
    - Seliger, Joan and Gustau - Jasper Johns, circa 1992 (Box 160, Folder 28)
    - Selkowitz, Judith, 1989 (Box 160, Folder 29)
    - Seriaal, 1970-1973 (Box 160, Folder 30)
    - Servodidio, Joseph, circa 1992 (Box 160, Folder 31)
    - Seward and Kissel, 1990 (Box 160, Folder 32)
    - Seydoux, Thomas - Andy Warhol, circa 1992 (Box 160, Folder 33)
    - Shachat, Steven, 1992 (Box 160, Folder 34)
    - Shands, Al, 1991 (Box 160, Folder 35)
    - Shapiro, Joe - Jasper Johns, circa 1992 (Box 160, Folder 36)
    - Sharafian, Steven, 1989 (Box 160, Folder 37)
    - Shaw, Lauren, 1980 (Box 160, Folder 38)
    - Sheehan, Susan, 1993 (Box 160, Folder 39)
    - Sheehan, Susan - Ellsworth Kelly, 1992 (Box 160, Folder 40)
    - Sherrod, Dan, circa 1992 (Box 160, Folder 41)
    - Shew, Sarah, 1990 (Box 160, Folder 42)
    - Shore, Lenore, 1990 (Box 160, Folder 43)
    - Shulman, Donna F., 1990 (Box 160, Folder 44)
    - Siden, Franklin - Offering List, 1993 (Box 160, Folder 45)
    - Siegel, Carl, 1988-1989 (Box 160, Folder 46)
    - Siegten, Bernard, 1990 (Box 160, Folder 47)
    - Silber, Herbert B., 1973 (Box 160, Folder 48)
    - Silberman, Jerry, 1989 (Box 160, Folder 49)
    - The Silver Image Gallery, 1978-1981 (Box 160, Folder 50)
    - Simoens, Andre, 1990 (Box 160, Folder 51)
    - Singh, Ranbir - Galerie 27, 1977 (Box 160, Folder 52)
    - Skelton, Annette Cone - Robert Rauschenberg, 1993 (Box 160, Folder 53)
    - Skelton, Marlys, 1976 (Box 160, Folder 54)
    - Skowhegan School of Paintings and Sculpture, 1990 (Box 160, Folder 55)
    - Smith, Graham, 1970-1971, 1974 (Box 160, Folder 56)
    - Smith, Joshua P., 1989 (Box 160, Folder 57)
    - Smith, Sharon, circa 1980 (Box 160, Folder 58)
    - Smoak, David, 1979-1981 (Box 160, Folder 59)
    - Snoddy, Stephen, 1990 (Box 160, Folder 60)
    - Snyder, Alice, 1989 (Box 160, Folder 61)
    - Sodergren, David, 1990 (Box 160, Folder 62)
    - Sofeico, Henry, 1989 (Box 160, Folder 63)
    - Software Creations, Incorporated, 1989 (Box 160, Folder 64)
    - Solway, Arthur - Carl Solway Gallery, 1990, 1992 (Box 160, Folder 65)
    - Solway, Carl, 1969, 1972-1974 (Box 160, Folder 66)
    - Sonnabend, Ileana, 1970-1974 (Box 160, Folder 67)
    - Sonneman, Eve, 1989 (Box 160, Folder 68)
    - Sonnenborn, Donald, 1993 (Box 160, Folder 69)
    - Sotheby's, 1990, 1992, 1994 (Box 160, Folder 70)
    - Sotheby's Educational Studies, 1993 (Box 160, Folder 71)
    - Souyun Yi Gallery, 1989 (Box 160, Folder 72)
    - Special Arts Fund for Emergencies, 1992 (Box 160, Folder 73)
    - Special Arts Fund for Emergencies Portfolio, 1992 (Box 160, Folder 74)
    - Special Impressions Gallery, 1990 (Box 160, Folder 75)
    - Specialty Signs Company, 1993 (Box 160, Folder 76)
    - Speichler, Louis, 1970-1973, 1979 (Box 160, Folder 77)
    - Speiller, William M. - Jacobs and Speiller, 1969-1973 (Box 160, Folder 78)
    - Spennato, Edna - David Salle, 1992 (Box 160, Folder 79)
    - Spiritus, Susan, 1977-1980 (Box 160, Folder 80)
    - Staatsgalerie Stuttgart, 1971-1972 (Box 160, Folder 81)
    - Staditsche Kunsthalle, 1972 (Box 160, Folder 82)
    - Stamatopoulos, Evangelos D., 1992 (Box 160, Folder 83)
    - Stamm, Alan, 1972, 1978-1979 (Box 160, Folder 84)
    - Standard Graphics, 1990 (Box 160, Folder 85)
    - Stark, Larry, 1971-1972, 1989 (Box 160, Folder 86)
    - Stein, Margot F., 1991 (Box 160, Folder 87)
    - Steinberg, Elaine, 1990 (Box 160, Folder 88)
    - Steinhardt, Judith, 1990, 1992 (Box 160, Folder 89)
    - Steinkamp, Roderic, 1989-1991 (Box 160, Folder 90)
    - Steinmetz, Don - Jasper Johns, circa 1993 (Box 160, Folder 91)
    - Stella, Frank, 1979 (Box 160, Folder 92)
    - Stellar Graphics, 1992-1993 (Box 160, Folder 93)
    - Stenstrand, Lennart - Storgatan 25, 1977 (Box 160, Folder 94)
    - Stern, Fred, 1990 (Box 160, Folder 95)
    - Stoller, John, 1977-1978 (Box 160, Folder 96)
    - Stone, Spencer D., 1978-1979 (Box 160, Folder 97)
    - Strauber, Frank, 1993-1994 (Box 160, Folder 98)
    - Straus, Philip A. - Roy Lichtenstein, 1992 (Box 160, Folder 99)
    - Strauss, Joyce and Edward, 1970, 1978-1981 (Box 160, Folder 100)
    - Strauss, Richard, 1992 (Box 160, Folder 101)
    - Strongin, Mrs., 1990 (Box 160, Folder 102)
    - Struve, Deborah and William, 1972-1973, 1977 (Box 160, Folder 103)
    - Studio International, 1970-1973 (Box 160, Folder 104)
    - Subastas Fortuny, 1990 (Box 160, Folder 105)
    - Sullivan, Thomas F., 1973-1974 (Box 160, Folder 106)
    - Susanne Hilberry Gallery - Ed Ruscha, 1992 (Box 160, Folder 107)
    - Swart, H. L., 1978 (Box 160, Folder 108)
    - Swift, Mary, 1979 (Box 160, Folder 109)
    - T, 1970-1981 (Box 160, Folder 110)
    - Taylor, Amy, 1991 (Box 160, Folder 111)
    - Tel Aviv Museum of Art, 1992 (Box 160, Folder 112)
    - Texann Ivy Gallery, 1989 (Box 160, Folder 113)
    - Texann Ivy Gallery - Andy Warhol, 1989-1990 (Box 160, Folder 114)
    - Texas Gallery, 1977-1980 (Box 160, Folder 115)
    - Thomas Erben Gallery - Richard Serra, circa 1992 (Box 160, Folder 116)
    - Thomas, Tamara B., 1981 (Box 160, Folder 117)
    - Thompson, Carole - Andy Warhol, circa 1993 (Box 160, Folder 118)
    - Timothy D. Kehr Gallery, 1993 (Box 160, Folder 119)
    - Titze, Monika, 1993 (Box 160, Folder 120)
    - Tolarno Galleries, 1973 (Box 160, Folder 121)
    - Tordoir, Guus, 1978-1980 (Box 160, Folder 122)
    - Travelling Light, 1979-1981 (Box 160, Folder 123)
    - Treffer, Susanne - Roy Lichtenstein, 1992 (Box 160, Folder 124)
    - Trepanier, Yves - List, 1993 (Box 160, Folder 125)
    - Trisorio, Pasquale, 1972, 1977-1978 (Box 160, Folder 126)
    - Tucker, Anne, 1977-1981 (Box 160, Folder 127)
    - Tucker, Jean S. - University of Missouri, 1990 (Box 160, Folder 128)
    - The Twenty-First Century Gallery Limited, 1971, 1977, 1979 (Box 160, Folder 129)
    - Tyler Graphics Ltd., 1978-1980 (Box 160, Folder 130)
    - U, 1970-1974, 1977-1981 (Box 160, Folder 131)
    - Ufficio Dell'Arte, 1980 (Box 160, Folder 132)
    - University Galleries - Robert Rauschenberg, 1972-1973 (Box 160, Folder 133)
    - University of Illinois, 1989 (Box 160, Folder 134)
    - University of Iowa, Museum of Art - Jasper Johns/Andy Warhol, 1970-1971 (Box 160, Folder 135)
    - University of Missouri, 1990 (Box 160, Folder 136)
    - University of New Mexico, 1974, 1978 (Box 160, Folder 137)
    - University of Regina, 1977 (Box 160, Folder 138)
    - University of Rhode Island, 1977-1978 (Box 160, Folder 139)
    - University of South Florida Art Museum, 1988, 1990-1991 (Box 160, Folder 140)
    - Upton, Gordon, 1978-1979 (Box 160, Folder 141)
    - V, 1970-1974, 1976-1981 (Box 160, Folder 142)
    - Van Brunt, Terry - Andy Warhol, circa 1993 (Box 160, Folder 143)
    - Van De Weghe, Eric, 1991-1992 (Box 160, Folder 144)
    - Van De Weghe-Delmote, Gabriel and Jacqueline - List, 1992 (Box 160, Folder 145)
    - van der Marck, Jan - Robert Rauschenberg, 1971 (Box 160, Folder 146)
    - Van Dyjk, Pablo, 1992 (Box 160, Folder 147)
    - Van Vleck, David, 1988 (Box 160, Folder 148)
    - Venet, Bernar, 1990, 1992 (Box 160, Folder 149)
    - Viart Corporation - Andy Warhol, 1993 (Box 160, Folder 150)
    - Vincent G. Kling and Partners, 1973 (Box 160, Folder 151)
    - Vision Gallery of Photography, 1979-1981 (Box 160, Folder 152)
    - Visual Studies Workshop, 1979-1980 (Box 160, Folder 153)
    - von Matthiessen, Maria, 1976-1977 (Box 160, Folder 154)
    - Voron, Helen, 1992 (Box 160, Folder 155)
    - W, 1969-1974, 1977-1978 (Box 160, Folder 156)
    - W, 1979-1981 (Box 160, Folder 157)
    - The Waddington Galleries, 1972-1973 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Waddington Graphics, 1990 (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Wagner, Marie-Christine, 1992 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Wagstaff, Sam - Detroit Institute of Arts, 1970 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - [Wakatalú, Mieka], 1990 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Wake Forest University, 1977, 1989, 1992-1993 (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Walker Art Center, 1970-1971, 1977-1979, 1991 (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - Walker, John Alan, 1988 (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - Wallens, Donald E., 1970-1971 (Box 161, Folder 9)
    - Walster, Nicholas, circa 1990 (Box 161, Folder 10)
    - Ward, Ron, 1980-1981 (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - Warhol, Andy - New Price List, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 12)
    - Waverly Multiples, 1970-1972 (Box 161, Folder 13)
    - Wawrzyniak, Udo, 1978-1979 (Box 161, Folder 14)
    - Wegner, Allison, 1988 (Box 161, Folder 15)
    - Weiner, Karen and Howard, 1989 (Box 161, Folder 16)
    - Weinstein, Ira, 1993 (Box 161, Folder 17)
    - Weiss, Jeffrey, 1979-1980 (Box 161, Folder 18)
    - Weissmann, Ann and Jerald, 1990-1992 (Box 161, Folder 19)
    - Welsh Arts Council - Andy Warhol, 1970-1971 (Box 161, Folder 20)
    - Wenaas, Thomas J., 1980-1981 (Box 161, Folder 21)
    - Werkstatt fur Photographie, 1977-1981 (Box 161, Folder 22)
    - Werner, Pepper, 1990 (Box 161, Folder 23)
    - Westreich, Thea, 1991 (Box 161, Folder 24)
    - Wetterling, Bjorn - Wetterling Gallery, 1990 (Box 161, Folder 25)
    - Wexner Center for the Arts, 1992 (Box 161, Folder 26)
    - Whatcom Museum, 1990 (Box 161, Folder 27)
    - White, James P., 1977-1978 (Box 161, Folder 28)
    - White, Martha, 1979-1980 (Box 161, Folder 29)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1970, 1976-1977, 1979, 1988, 1990 (Box 161, Folder 30)
    - The Wichita Art Museum, 1970-1972 (Box 161, Folder 31)
    - Wiegmann, Richard - Concordia College, 1992 (Box 161, Folder 32)
    - Wier, Richard - Robert Rauschenberg, circa 1992 (Box 161, Folder 33)
    - Wierzbowski, Richard, 1989 (Box 161, Folder 34)
    - William Doyle Galleries, 1990 (Box 161, Folder 35)
    - Wine, Hadley J. - Roy Lichtenstein, 1992 (Box 161, Folder 36)
    - Wirth, Marie Louise, 1989 (Box 161, Folder 37)
    - Wirtz, Stephen, 1978-1980 (Box 161, Folder 38)
    - Winn Galleries - Robert Rauschenberg/Frank Stella, 1970 (Box 161, Folder 39)
    - Wits Air Cargo Service, 1971, 1974 (Box 161, Folder 40)
    - Wofsy, Alan, 1989-1990 (Box 161, Folder 41)
    - Wolf, Peter, 1990, 1992 (Box 161, Folder 42)
    - Wolgin, William, 1969-1971 (Box 161, Folder 43)
    - Woodman and Robinson Studio G - List, 1993 (Box 161, Folder 44)
    - The Woodward Foundation, 1969-1972 (Box 161, Folder 45)
    - Wright, Bagley, 1980 (Box 161, Folder 46)
    - WR Keating and Company, 1978-1979 (Box 161, Folder 47)
    - XYZ, 1969-1973, 1978-1980 (Box 161, Folder 48)
    - Xart Collection, 1971-1972 (Box 161, Folder 49)
    - Yarlow/Salzman Gallery, 1978-1980 (Box 161, Folder 50)
    - Young, Greg, 1990 (Box 161, Folder 51)
    - Young Hoffman Gallery, 1979-1981 (Box 161, Folder 52)
    - Youssef, Freddy and Magda Streuli, 1992-1993 (Box 161, Folder 53)
    - Yun, Helen, 1992 (Box 161, Folder 54)
    - Yvon Lambert Gallery, 1986, 1990 (Box 161, Folder 55)
    - Zabriskie Gallery, 1976-1979 (Box 161, Folder 56)
    - Zanatta, Joe, 1990 (Box 161, Folder 57)
    - Zavala, Miquel, 1990 (Box 161, Folder 58)
    - Zweibel, Renee and Stuart, 1989-1990, 1992 (Box 161, Folder 59)
    - Zwirner, Rudolph - Galerie Rudolf Zwirner, 1969-1972 (Box 161, Folder 60)
  - Administrative Files, 1969-1993; 7.2
    Administrative files document daily operations of Castelli Graphics and include advertising materials, consignment and loan agreements, inventory lists, price lists, personnel files, appointment books, shipping records, and information regarding specific artists and their artwork. There are numerous files documenting joint ventures with Multiples, Inc. Addition scattered business correspondence, sales records, and financial records are also found in this subseries. Folders are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - 578 Broadway Floor Plan, circa 1980s (Box 161, Folder 61)
    - Abrams Book Orders, 1991 (Box 161, Folder 62)
    - Advertising, circa 1975-1977, 1981 (Box 161, Folder 63)
    - Advertising, 1990-1991 (Box 161, Folder 64)
    - Advertising, 1991 (Box 161, Folder 65)
    - Appointment Book, 1989; 2 Folders (Box 161, Folder 66-67)
    - Appointment Book, 1990; 2 Folders (Box 161, Folder 68-69)
    - Appraisal Analysis, 1993 (Box 161, Folder 70)